respected and seen but an increase in
technology need not bear a higher degree
of complexity do you agree with that or
not I I've like I've talked with my
father about this like my dad's like I
don't like these new cars they're so
complicated I immediately shut him up I
said what are you talking about it the
the the the uh the false statement that
with new
technology necessitates increased
complexity is something that I think has
harmed people like we we always assume
something better requires more effort
and that's bear with me I think that's a
beautiful tenant of our modern society
and why it's sometimes hard to see where
people are
building success and in those ways so